It starts here, doesn't it?
The journey to make my wish come true.
I'll do my best!
Kobato.
How do I do this again?
The simplest things in life
end up being the most difficult.
I just want to smile when I'm happy
and sing a song whenever I please.
Someone once told me, "Your
dream will come true someday."
But when exactly will that be?
I can't wait that long!
I spread my arms
on the count of one two three
and gather all the light in the world.
Tell me,
isn't there something I can do?
Even if someone hurts my feelings,
I'll keep running toward the light.
Even if I trip, fall, and cry my eyes out, I still believe.
Although it may seem silly...
I believe in tomorrow.
Production
The Kobato Protection Group
...Wishful Girl.
Kobato...
Yes, Ioryogi?
We've finally arrived in the human world where humans reside.
Understand?
Yes.
From here on, your wish will or will not be granted depending on how well you do.
You understand that too, right?
Yes, of course.
If you understand...
Then why the hell are we in this cramped place?!
Look, it's like we're in a hideout having a secret meeting!
It's fun!
You're the only one who's having fun!
Kobato Hanato!
Yes?
What's your wish?!
I have a place I want to go to.
What do you have to do in order to make your wish come true?
I have to collect a lot of broken hearts into a flask.
Before that?
I have to get a flask!
And what do you have to do to get it?
I have to pass a test to see if I can live here or not!
That's right.
For one whole day, you have to fit into the
human world and display human common sense.
The test already began.
And I'm your proctor.
Did you get that?!
Y-Yes, I did.
You'll be graded on how well you display human common sense through your actions.
Show me what you've got, Kobato!
Act like a human at a park during Spring!
Get moving!
Okay!
How was that, Ioryogi?
What are you, a hibernating bag worm?!
For crying out loud, you can't even act like a human being at a park.
Sorry...
And also-
Man, why is the trash still here?
I'm going to miss the bus...
I'm sorry.
Don't worry about it.
Shoot! I'm going to be late!
Ioryogi?
She dropped it.
Oh, here's your next test!
What're you going to do about that trash bag? Show me.
Okay...
The dump... The dump...
Found it!
Right here...
Right here?
I'm going to...
You're going to?
Be thoughtful and throw out as little trash as possible.
The crows...
They have their eyes on the trash.
Hurry up and throw it away or they'll pick you clean.
The crows have their eyes on...
Be thoughtful and throw out as little trash as possible.
...the trash.
Here you go, crows!
What the hell are you doing?!
That scared me.
What the hell were you trying to do?!
The crows were hungry and the sign said "Please be thoughtful".
You should change your name to Dobato!
That's not nice.
Hey, you.
Alone?
Wanna get a drink?
A drink?
There's a pretty good place around the corner.
Hitting on her, huh.
It'll be our treat.
Really? Thank you very much!
Let's go.
Okay!
Isn't this great, Ioryogi?
You idiot!
Why are you following them?!
But they're treating me...
Are you two okay?
You're not hurt, right?
You bitch! What did you just do?
Hey, you're asking for it!
Annoying kids.
She already has a guy!
Umm... Thank-
Don't get carried away when guys give you attention.
I'm not!
Well, I have a good idea why he thinks that.
Thank god today's a nice day.
There'll be a lot of people coming to see the flowers, so we're going to be busy.
Right, Fujimoto?
Right.
Here.
Okay.
It was a really cute cat!
Enjoy.
I'll take these plates away.
Thanks.
He's so cool.
Hey, wanna ask him for his name?
Come on!
You're so cold, Fujimoto.
You'd be pretty popular if you smiled a bit more.
Whatever, I don't care.
You're so not cute.
Sorry, I forgot to turn it off.
Yomogi Nursery
Hello, Fujimoto speaking.
What's the matter, Ms. Sayaka?
Those assholes came by again?
Hang on, I'll be right there.
Sorry, Boss! There's an emergency...
I wonder what this is.
There's a lot of people here, Ioryogi.
It's probably a cherry blossom festival.
I gotta say, something here smells really nice.
Let's go check it out.
Okay, let's go!
They're in full bloom.
Isn't it so beautiful?
Hey, could you pass that here?
Okay, no problem.
Thank you!
Here I go!
What's going on?!
I'm sorry!
No use crying over spilled milk.
I'm really sorry!
I'm already running low on staff...
Please let me help you!
I'll pay you back by helping you!
One beer, please!
All right.
Man, my part timer had to run earlier.
So you're a great help.
Really?
I'm glad I could be of some help!
It's rare that she does this well.
Hey, my hotpot still isn't ready?
Coming!
Here you go.
You listening?
Yeah, I am.
Enjoy.
Sorry, could you help me add stuff to it?
Thanks.
Then you see...
I'm adding stuff... to the hotpot?!
This can be a test too.
I'll take a good look at her culinary skills.
You're not supposed to add
stuff before the water boils!
You can't add the meat yet!
Wait, why are you adding milk?!
Because it's nutritious-
No chocolate!
Sweet things will cheer you up!
No natto!
This is what hell looks like.
B-But it'd be a waste not to eat it...
Huh?
It's good!
You're right!
Wanna try it?
It's really good.
Yeah.
Tastes great!
Yeah, it does!
Young lady, I'll make this our special dish!
Thank you very much.
You're really capable despite your age.
Now I wanna try it too...
But she's just a moron.
The common sense you displayed while making the hotpot deserves a 0.
What?
But it turned out to be pretty good, so I'll give you a 40.
No way...
Don't cry, don't cry.
What's wrong?
He won't stop crying...
I'm sorry.
Don't worry, it's not your fault.
But...
He's always like this at night.
I always bring him here so he won't annoy our neighbors.
But he won't fall asleep until he's tired of crying.
I see...
His mother used to spend a lot of time with him...
When he cries, she sings him a song until he stops crying.
Where's his mom?
She's working hard so she can support her child.
That's why I need to take good care of him right now.
I tried singing to him, but he won't stop crying...
Please let me sing.
I'll sing for him.
I might not be able to sing like his mother, but...
Please do.
Okay!
I'll try my best!
The flowers that bloom during Spring
and the endless sky of Summer
are both brilliantly engraved into my heart...
Don't worry, I'm already back at the store.
So don't worry about-
Even on rainy days with the windows closed,
No, there's someone...
the overflowing light in my heart soars in the sky.
Please guide me,
O' faraway voice.
Like smiles...
Like songs...
It's the sound of the wind resonating.
Whether it's happiness or sadness,
Singing is the only thing Kobato's good at.
I'll shoulder it all and strive forward.
Well, that makes her similar to Kohaku.
These are the things we both hold in our hands.
Wow...
Umm, I...
It was beautiful.
It seems like he stopped crying.
Thank goodness.
It's thanks to you.
Hey, please sing again!
Yeah! Sing more!
There's a stage over there! Let's go!
Hey, come on!
We got so many gifts.
They were thank you gifts for singing.
Accepting them was the right thing to do.
So...
What about the test?
So, the test...
Kobato Hanato!
Y-Yes!
You acted like an idiot for the first half.
And you got lucky with the hotpot you made in the second half.
But your singing was okay.
Then...!
You failed!
You just said my singing was okay!
You were awful during the first half.
That's mean! You're horrible!
But I tried my best!
Well, you were on the margin.
Too bad.
No way...
Young lady.
Oh, it's you.
Good evening.
Good evening to you too, little songstress.
I'm glad I bumped into you again.
Thank you very much.
I really wanted to express my gratitude.
It's the first time he's been so happy from listening to someone other than his mother sing.
But the moment I thought he's cheered up, he fell asleep.
I'm really sorry for leaving without saying thank you.
Oh, don't worry about that.
Your singing was beautiful.
I would love to listen to it again next time.
Okay.
Good night.
O-Oh, good night!
Kobato Hanato!
Yes?
You passed.
This is...
The flask, right?
It's real, right?
Yeah, you got a hundred from the old lady thanking you.
So you passed.
Is this the real, real thing?
Give it back if you don't want it!
I do! I do!
If I heal broken hearts and fill this flask up with heart fragments...
Your wish will come true.
However, you just got your hands on the flask.
Yes.
Kobato Hanato, what's your wish?
I have a place I want to go to.
What do you have to do in order to make your wish come true?
I have to use this flask to
collect a lot of broken hearts.
Listen up, you start here.
You're still far away from your goal!
I know! I'll do my best!
Are you sure, Dobato? You don't look like you mean it!
Hey, that's really mean!
Dobato
My name is Kobato. Kobato Hanato!
Dobato is good enough.
If you don't like it, I'll call you Dabada.
Dabada
Dabada?!
Even though we all want to fly,
we're being deceived by gravity.
In reality, everybody can already fly.
The reason why that child looks so sad
might be because she left her shadow somewhere.
If so...
If telling you "Thank you",
or hearing "Thank you" just makes you smile,
then doing those things will make me happy.
And they'll make you happy too.
Don't worry, we're together.
It's mysterious as to why tears roll down
even though I'm happy.
Next
...The Confeito's Shine.